"Kissing at High Tide"
You see clearly
This is what you want
today
You just need to feel my temperature
Kneel down
take off your clothes
Why are you so hot?
Because I took a shower
take a bath
But didn’t you take a cold shower?
It's also possible
come to me
call you over
2000 USD
In addition to paying off my mother’s surgery fee
How will you spend the rest of the money?
I want to go to Florence
Want to see the real Renaissance
Florence?
For $2,000?
Yeah
Because I want to see the real Florence
We only sign a physical contract
now
Do you want to sell your soul to me too?
What is the contract?
like this
Can I sign a contract with blood?
Even if you're hungry, you can't eat without my permission.
This is a bad habit
if you want to eat
Tell me with your mouth
like this
So good
Don't worry, you'll choke.
From now on you can only eat what I give you
Han Zaixun
Are you really a chaebol?
Not a cold-blooded animal?
Why would you still eat kimchi pot?
you also each other
Isn’t it said that art students survive by inspiration?
He even eats this kind of bread
eat this
This is much healthier
But
I heard
You're trying to pick up girls
Played Chopin all night in front of the Conservatory of Music
You have a very rich imagination
Please use this talent for painting
Also
Not to pick up girls
It's because I'm playing truth or dare
If you say this kind of nonsense again next time
I'll just give you an iced Americano
Why is it iced American style?
Won't you answer me?
I don't like drinking iced Americano
Eat
©2025 SEEKMedia All Rights Reserved